gface.com 2012-04-13

# Play. Together. Live.

### I. GFACE Online Privacy Policy: Introduction

GFACE GmbH and its subsidiary companies (GFACE) respect the privacy rights of consumers and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted this global Privacy Policy to explain how we store and use personal and non-personal information we collect online on our websites, during your use of our online products and/or services (including online game play) and on mobile platforms.

#### II. What is Personal Information and when does GFACE collect It?

GFACE collects both personal and non-personal consumer information. Personal information collected by GFACE is discussed below in this section. Non-personal information is discussed below in Section III.

A. Personal Information Collected By GFACE  
Personal information is information that identifies you and that may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. GFACE may collect personal information from our online visitors during:

  * Gaming and other user behavior including gaming results;
  * Warranty registration and requests;
  * Customer support and/or technical service requests;
  * Player match up and other head-to-head online competitions;
  * Registration for games and/or special game-specific events;
  * Newsletter subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns;
  * Registration for GFACE and/or other service accounts;
  * Product, service and/or subscription orders;
  * Service requests from third party service providers on our site; and
  * Otherwise through use of our software, mobile or online services where personal information is required for use and/or participation.

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, user name, email address, password, phone number, home address, birth date, mobile phone number and credit card information but will only be saved when needed. You will be specifically notified in case of irregular collection of data. GFACE also may maintain log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that may be assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we use log files to monitor traffic on our websites and to troubleshoot technical problems and will delete IP addresses after 7 days. In the event of user abuse of our websites, however, we may block certain IP addresses. If available, IP addresses and console IDs may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Service.

B. Personal Information Provided To GFACE By Third Parties.

1\. Other Information Collected From Third Parties  
We may also receive other personal information from third parties in connection with the operation and distribution of our products and services as well as market and demographic studies that we use to supplement personal information provided directly by you. As with all other information, we use this data only for purposes consistent with this policy.

III. What Is Non-Personal Information and When Does GFACE Collect It?  
Non-personal information, alone, cannot be used to identify or contact you. GFACE collects non-personal information about your use of our online and mobile products and services both on our website and in the course of game play and software usage (on PC, mobile and console platforms).

A. What Types of Non-Personal Information Does GFACE Collect?  
When you use GFACE online and mobile products and services or you play our games on your PC or console, we may collect certain non-personal demographic information including gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, mobile device. We also collect other non-personal information such as feature usage, game play statistics and scores, user rankings and click paths as well as other data that you may provide in surveys, via your account preferences and online profiles or through purchases, for instance. We may also receive either non-personal or public information from third parties in connection with market and demographic studies that we use to supplement personal information provided directly by you.

B. How Does GFACE Collect Non-Personal Information?  
GFACE collects non-personal information in addition to personal information when you actively provide it in the context of various online and mobile activities including online and mobile purchases, game registration and marketing surveys, for instance. In addition, we might use cookies and other technologies to passively collect non-personal demographic information, personalize your experience on our sites and monitor advertisements and other activities.

1\. Cookies  
Cookies are small files applied to your Internet browser to track movements within websites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store, pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, for example. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. We collect information on what games are played, how much time is spent playing the games and which ads or links are clicked. Some of our sites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are applied by our ad companies, and GFACE does not have access to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent.

We may also use flash cookies, also known as "local shared objects," on our sites that employ Flash technology. Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies and are used to remember the site's settings to personalize the look and feel of the site. Flash cookies only collect data in the aggregate. Like normal cookies, Flash cookies are represented as small files on your computer. One method of preventing Flash cookies from being placed is to adjust your preferences in the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at [www.macromedia.com](http://www.macromedia.com/).

Please note that this privacy policy covers the use of cookies by GFACE only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

2\. Third Party Ad Serving Technology  
The companies that serve the ads that may appear on our websites may also collect information regarding your activities online, including the sites you visit. For more information on such services or to opt out of those services, please visit such services’ websites.

3\. Analytic Metrics Tool and Other Technologies  
GFACE also uses its own proprietary analytic metrics tool and other analytics technologies to collect non-personal information when you use our online products and services and/or play our games on your PC, console and/or mobile device.

IV. What Happens To The Information GFACE Collects?  
A. How GFACE Uses Your Information  
GFACE uses your information to operate GFACE’s games, fulfill your specific requests, and purchase orders and to send you purchase confirmation and other account-related information. In addition, if you choose to receive communications from us about GFACE products and news, the personal information you provide will allow us to send you messages about things including new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests and events of interest. You may also later opt out of this service from GFACE. Your participation in tournaments or other online game events is also conditional upon our collection, use, storage, transmission and public display of statistical data (such as your scores, rankings and achievements) generated through your participation.

B. Will GFACE Share My Information With Third Parties?  
GFACE will never share your personal information with third parties without your consent. We may, however, share non-personal data in the aggregate (in a form that does not personally identify you) with third parties. You may also opt in to allow GFACE to share your personal information with companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To opt out of further communications from a marketing partner or sponsor with whom your information has been shared, please contact that partner or sponsor directly. From time to time, GFACE employs third party contractors to collect personal information on our behalf to provide email delivery, product, or promotional fulfillment, contest administration, credit card processing, shipping or other services on our sites. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to our contractors. We ask some third party contractors, such as credit agencies or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to us for our own marketing and demographic studies, so that we can consistently improve our sites and related advertising to better meet our visitors' needs and preferences. When our third party contractors collect and/or have access to the personal information you provide to GFACE, GFACE requires that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by GFACE. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your specific consent.

You will be notified before your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. We may also disclose personal information to law enforcement, or the appropriate civil authorities to enforce legal rights and comply with the law, or to comply with an order from a government entity or other competent authority, or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, combat fraud and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on GFACE.

V. Where Is The Information Held?  
GFACE is a global organization and the majority of the computer systems on which GFACE collects, stores, and uses the information it collects or receives are based in the Germany. Under limited circumstances, we may utilize data storage facilities located in the European Union, the USA and/or Asia. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by GFACE in Germany and in other countries, including countries both in and outside the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

VI. How Does GFACE Protect Your Personal Information?  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and in storage. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact the Privacy Policy Administrator via email at dataprivacy[at]gface.com VII. Review, Correction of Your Information, Requesting Removal from Mailing Lists and Deactivating Your Account You can correct, update or delete your account information at any time by logging on our site and navigating to "My Account," "View My Profile" or other account settings. Should you be unable to log in or are participating in the GFACE Closed BETA contact dataprivacy[at]gface.com. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

VIII. Public Information Including User Generated Content, Online Forums, Blogs and Profiles  
You may choose to disclose information about yourself in the course of contributing user generated content to GFACE sites or games or in public online chat rooms, blogs, message boards, user "profiles" for public view or in similar forums on our sites. Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit in the course of these public activities can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

If you post a video, image or photo on one of our sites for public view you should be aware that these may be viewed, collected, copied and/or used by other users without your consent. We are not responsible for the videos, images or photos that you choose to submit to GFACE services. Please see our regulations at www.gface.com/terms on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our Service.

IX. Third Party Sites.  
Our Services may contain advertising or services which link to other websites such as Twitter, Facebook and YouTube. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the GFACE site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as GFACE. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to a GFACE site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

X. Products Offered In Partnership with Third Party(s)  
Members may register for other services from our site(s). Certain products and/or services available on our service are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.

XI. Contact Information  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the GFACE Privacy Policy Administrator at dataprivacy[at]gface.com.
